Guide to the 99¢ Floating Theatre Festival Records, 1971-1981 CTC.1987.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
99¢ Floating Theatre Festival Records
1971-1981
ULS Archives & Special Collections
99¢ Floating Theatre Festival.
CTC.1987.01
5 Linear Feet
The 99¢ Floating Theatre brought remarkable diversity to the local theater scene by importing small performance groups such as unusual professional theater, dance, and music troupes or individuals to Pittsburgh. This collection documents the activities of the organization and the performers that it presented.
(11 boxes)
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
History
The 99¢ Floating Theatre was a University of Pittsburgh affiliated organization, founded by Professor Richard Mennen, and brought remarkable diversity to the local theater scene by importing small performance groups such as unusual professional theater, dance, and music troupes or individuals to Pittsburgh. For the first few years Mennen was the entire staff of the organization. The name is based on the 99¢ price of a ticket and the fact that the performances were held at a variety of spaces and locations such as gyms, dance studios, churches, etc., avoiding the high prices of many theaters. The group presented dozens of eclectic groups and performers between the years 1973-1983. All the companies or performers could be considered avant-garde or experimental in nature. In 1977, Professor Leon Katz replaced Mennen as director.
Previous Citation
99¢ Floating Theatre Festival Records, CTC.1987.01, Curtis Theatre Collection, Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh
99¢ Floating Theatre Festival Collection, CTC.19, Curtis Theatre Collection, Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh
Acquisition Information
Gift of University of Pittsburgh Theatre Arts Department.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into three series:
Series I. Season Operation Files, 1974-1981
Series II. Other Operation Files, 1971-1981
Series III. Scrapbooks, 1974-1981
Scope and Content Notes
The 99¢ Floating Theatre Festival Records are arranged into three series. All the materials are paper-based and include correspondence, memos, grant applications, budget reports, photographs, etc. The Season Operation Files series is divided into several subseries for each season starting with 1973/1974 through 1981/1982. There is also one oversized scrapbook that contains newspaper clippings, small posters, programs, etc.
Theater programs; Clippings (Information artifacts); Correspondence; Experimental theater -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Financial records; Mime; Performance art -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Performing arts -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Photographs; Puppet theater -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Puppet theater companies -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Scrapbooks; Theater; Theater -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; 99¢ Floating Theatre Festival.; Bread and Puppet Theater.; Carroll, Pat, 1927-; Chew, Martha; Chong, Ping; Feit, Ken, 1940-1981; Fratti, Mario, 1927-; Grotowski, Jerzy, 1933-1999; Illusion Theater Company.; Ludlam, Charles; Mayer, Jerry; Organic Theatre Company.; Performance Group.; Red Clay Ramblers.; Ridiculous Theatrical Company.; San Francisco Mime Troupe.; Theatre Rhinoceros (San Francisco, Calif.).; Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival (Pittsburgh, Pa.).; University of Pittsburgh. Department of Theatre Arts.
- Season Operation Files, 1974-1981; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  The Season Operation files are broken down into nine subseries. Each subseries contains the files associated with a given theatre season of the 99¢ Floating Theatre Festival. Within each subseries, the files are arranged alphabetically by title. Nearly every season has financial information, grant applications, correspondence, etc.
  - 1973-1974 Season, 1.
    - Financial records, November 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1974-1975 Season, 2.
    - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Financial records, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Grotowski, Jerzy – Lecture, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Nationality Room members, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1975-1976 Season, 3.
    - Appeal for funding (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Financial records, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Kuku Ryku, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - National Endowment for the Arts - Grant application, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts – Calendar of theater performances, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Performing artists requested by PA sponsors for 1975/76 season (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Proposals (unused) (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Theatre workshops (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1976-1977 Season, 4.
    - Alternate Theatre Companies (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Cynkutis, Zbigniew, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Financial records, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - National Endowment for the Arts - Expansion arts, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 1977-1978 Season, 5.
    - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Financial records, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Mabou Mines, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Medicine Show, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Mayer, Jerry in "Taudshow", 1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - National Endowment for the Arts - Narrative report (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - National Endowment for the Arts - Proposal, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - National Endowment for the Arts - Revised project grant application, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - National Endowment for the Arts - List of recipients for 1977/78, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts - Grant application, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts – Guidelines for Grant application, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Phone records print-outs, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Pitt news – Tear sheets and billing, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Ridiculous Theatrical Company – the Ventriloquist's Wife, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Space confirmations, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Squat Theatre, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1978-1979 Season, 6.
    - Accounts payable check procedure, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Alternate Roots, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - F.E.D.A.R.T. conference, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Financial Records, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - The Four Horsemen, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Graduate student task force - policy statement on TA's and TF's; admission requirements, February 1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Heinz endowment fund, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Mabou mines, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - National Endowment for the Arts – Grant, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - National Endowment for the Arts – Proposal, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - National endowment for the Arts – Revised grant, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts – Grant (N.E.A. & P.A.C. Pilot touring project), 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts – "Arts to the People" Conference, November 1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - The Performance Group, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Pitt Union Program Council (P.U.P.C.), 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Provisional Theatre Company, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Ridiculous Theatrical Company – Camille, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Schedule of events - partial (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Theatre of Mistakes, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Three Rivers Arts Festival, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - University of Pittsburgh – Faculty Development Grant Information (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - National Endowment for the Arts – Work experience internship grant (Don Marinelli), 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1979-1980 Season, 7.
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Dance Council of central Pennsylvania – The Danceletter, March 1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Financial Records, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Heinz endowment – grant request, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Little Nell - from the Rocky Horror Picture Show, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Meredith Monk, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - National Endowment for the Arts – Grant application, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - National Endowment for the Arts – Grant, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - National Endowment for the Arts – Institutional advancement grants (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - National Endowment for the Arts – Revised grant, #AO61994-79, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - New York City tour, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts – Dance touring grant for Meredith Monk, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts – Grant #5-37955, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh news items on arts, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Possible groups, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Ravine, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Ridiculous Theatrical Company – Bluebeard (The Enchanted Pig), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Royal Dancers and Musicians from the Kingdom of Bhutan – Clippings, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Royal Dancers and Musicians from the Kingdom of Bhutan - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Royal Dancers and Musicians from the Kingdom of Bhutan – Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Royal Dancers and Musicians from the Kingdom of Bhutan – Photos (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Royal Dancers and Musicians from the Kingdom of Bhutan – Program and marketing information, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Teaching development grant from the Office of Faculty Development, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Three black and three white refined jubilee minstrels, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1980-1981 Season, 8.
    - Arden, Marty - Alternate Roots, Zimbabwe Project – Correspondence, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Facets Performance Ensemble, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Financial records, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Fujian Puppet theatre from the People's Republic of China, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Independent Eye – T.A.P. Grant for $700.00, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - National Endowment for the Arts – Special Projects (Presenting organization grant), 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts – Financial and narrative reports for grant, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts – Jeff Weiss proposal to P.C.A., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts – Project Grant, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Squat Theatre, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Theatre Association of Pennsylvania – Contract, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Warsaw Mime Theatre, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 1981-1982 Season, 9.
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts – Guide to programs (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Other Operation Files, 1971-1981; II.
  This series contains files that were not attributed to a specific season in the history of the 99¢ Floating Theatre Festival. Most of the files in this series contain information on various national and international theatre companies that were considered or presented by the 99¢ Floating Theatre. The files are arranged in alphabetical order by subject.
  - Account #4-24930, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Account #4-25388 – Bills and printouts, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Actors lab – Hamilton, Ontario, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Akjalaaitis, JoAnne/Southern Exposures (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - American Revolutionary Road Company, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - American Theatre, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Amitin, Mark, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Arthur Cantor, Inc., 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Arthur Shafman International Ltd., 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Artservices, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Asia Society – Performing Arts Program, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Awasthi, Dr. Suresh, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - American Theatre Association Placement Service Bulletin, January 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Bicentennial proposals, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Body Politic Dream Theatre, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Bread and Puppet Theatre, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Brochure for Floating Theatre – Technical information, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Burmese National Theatre – Burmese music and Anyein (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Business committee for the Arts, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Carroll, Bob, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Carroll, Pat as Gertrude Stein, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Celebrations Mime Theatre, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Chew, Martha, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - City University of London – Arts Management Program, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Collaborative for the Arts in Pittsburgh Education or C.A.P.E., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Collaboratory Theatre, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Commedia del'Pinky – Photos (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Companhia de Teatre de Lisboa - International Theatre Exchange, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Court Dance Theatre and Music - Okinawa, Japan, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Cricot 2 Theatre Company, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Dandelion Productions, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Daniel Lewis Dance Repertory Company, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Entourage (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Feit, Ken - Ken the Fool, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Fiji Company, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Financial - Miscellaneous reports (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Fine Line Actor's Theatre, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Floating Theatre facts and history – For use in grant application (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Florida Studio Theatre, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Fools Company, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Fratti, Mario, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Future ideas for 99cent Floating Theatre (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Group listing (Experimental theatre companies available for touring), 1975 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Group Motion Media Theatre, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Harry - Dance Company, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Harvey, John, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Heinz Endowment budget and account #5-35898, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Heinz Foundation report on 99¢ Floating Theatre activities, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - History of the 99¢ Floating Theatre (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Hoechstetter, Harvey – Printing, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Hu Hung-Yen – Peking Opera performer, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Hughes, Richard and Walter Scott, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Illusion Theatre, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Independent Eye, 1975-1981 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - International Ballet and Festival Corporation, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - International Communication Agency – Educational and cultural affairs, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - International Theatre Institute – Newsletters, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Iowa Theatre Lab, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Janus Film Company, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Japan Arts, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Korea National Classical Institute – AAK Korean Court Music and Dance (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Kornfield, Larry – "Dr. Faustus lights the light", 1979 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Kraken, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Lawrence, Dan, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Le Plan K, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Library display cases – Forms, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Little Marrowbone, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Lost Nation Theatre (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Mailers – Forms for printing and mail, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - The Manhattan Project, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Marcus, Linda, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Mellon Educational Grant printouts #5-37058, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Melpo, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Metropolitan Cultural Alliance, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Movement work center, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - National Endowment for the Arts – Joint N.E.A. Pilot touring grant, proposal with Walter Arts Center, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - National Endowment for the Arts – Supply grant print-outs, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - National Artists Management Company, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - National Dance Company of Senegal - International Ballet Festival, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - NDWT Company - Canadian, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - New Directions in the Performing Arts - Canadian conference (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - New Theatre Festival - Baltimore, June 1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Organic Theatre Company, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Otrabunda Company, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Outreach possibilities (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Passaro, Bob - Fisher Scientific, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts – Advisory Panel with Dr. Richard Mennen of Theatre Arts Department, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts – General information, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts – Grant #5-36954, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts – Groups, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Palisades Theatre Company, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Pentacle Dance Management, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - People Energy - based with the Wilma Project in Philadelphia (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - People Show, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Performing arts for children, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Peripatetic Task Force, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Philadance / Philadelphia Dance Company, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Philly Rep. Co. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Phoenix Dance Theater, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Pieces Company, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Pigeon Drop Theatre, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Pilato, Joe, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Ping Chong, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Pittsburgh Laboratory Theatre – Theatre space, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Pittsburgh Regional Committee for the Arts, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Play Group, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Posnak, Paul, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Printouts #5-38691, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Provisional Theatre, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Public service announcements and press releases, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Quena, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - The Ramayana, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Red Clay Ramblers (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Red Mole Enterprise, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Resumes (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Rhode Island Feminist Theatre, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Sachiyo Ito – Japanese Kabuki (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Saeko Ichinohe – Japanese dancer (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - San Francisco Mime Troupe, 1976-1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Shaliko Company, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Shankar, Ravi (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Sherman, Robert (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Sherman, Stuart, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Siamsa - National Folk Theatre of Ireland, 1976-1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Smithsonian Performing Arts, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Sponsors in Western Pennsylvania, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Sports Pages, 1976-1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Stage One Theatre Lab, 1974-1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Stephen Foster Memorial Space, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Studio Theatre Task Force (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - The Talking Band, 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - T.A.P. / Theatre Association of Pennsylvania, 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - T.C.G. / Theatre Communications Group, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - T.R. Uthco, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - El Teatro Campesino Theatre Group, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Telephone bill print-outs, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Theatre de l'arbre, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Theatre Express, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Theatre Lab Project print-outs #4-24930, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Theatre Project - Baltimore, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Theatre Project Grant, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Theatre Rhinoceros / Gay Theatre San Francisco, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Theatre X, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - TNT Festival information, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Tom Johnson - Trinity Dance Management, 1972-1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Travel, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Universal Movement Theatre Repertory, 1972-1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Vanaver, Bill and Livia Drapkin, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Well Diggers Experimental Theatre Company, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Western Penitentiary – Contacts and information form, 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - The Wilma Project, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Wimmer, Wimmer & Dancers, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Scrapbooks, 1974-1981; III.
  This one oversized scrapbook encompasses the entire history of the 99¢ Floating Theatre Festival. Within it are newspaper clippings about the organization, reviews, small posters, marketing materials, programs, etc.
  - Scrapbook, 1974-1981 (Box 11)